

Trần Phước Thọ

Intern

: 0342024403

CAREER GOALS

My aim is to get practical experience for further development in my Commercial career. Especially, my specific area of interest is Strategic / Analysis Business roles in: Logistic, Supply Chain, Finace or E-Commerce. In addition, being selected into the company's official employee with professional qualifications and skills for ensuring the best dedication to the organization's growth is my long-term career goal.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF COMMERCIAL BUSINESS:

September 2017 - December 2021

VAN LANG UNIVERSITY - VLU HCM

Major: Commercial Business

Key Papers:

- International Logistics and Commercial

Key Developed Skills:

- Think logically.
- Dare to think and Dare to do with high responsibility.

CAREER HISTORY

INBOUND / OUTBOUND

August 2020 - November 2020

Tiki Join Stock Company:

Main responsibilities:

- Import & Export Goods
- Inventory Management

BUSINESS ASSISTANT

January 2020 - August 2020

Invi Bridge Company:

Main responsibilities:

- Planner
- Sourcing Producer
- Maintain contact with DHL for Export

Achievement:

- Having own Project

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

ACTIVITIES IN VLU CLUB

September 2018 – Now

MEMBER OF YOUNG BUSINESS:

Main responsibilities:

- Helping organize events and impart knowledge.

CHARITY IN CHIRSTMAS NIGHT:

MAIN ORGANIZATION OF "SAI GON OI 2021" FESTIVAL

- Scale: 3 or 4 diffirent club with at least 70 members MAIN ORAGANIZATION IN "SPRING EVENT 2021"

- Scale: 32 members of Young Business

CONTEST 2021

<u>Leader of CMO 2021 Ton Duc Thang University</u>:

Sacele

- All the University in South of Viet Nam

Achievement:

- Waiting for the Result

Leader of Vietnam PRO Supply Chain Challenge:

Sacele:

-Nationally

INTERN

0898023353

| trantho508@gmail.com

Mr/Mrs HR Officer Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Dear Mr/Mrs,

I am currently in my final year at Van Lang University completing the Bachelor of Commercial Business. I am writing to see if you would be interested in offering a Co-operative Education practicum to me.

The Co-operative Education practicum is designed to allow students to apply their academic learning to the workplace environment. This is a joint undertaking that involves me, my workplace manager and an academic supervisor from my university – Van Lang University (VLU). According to this Co-operative Education's timeline. Therefore, Co-operative Education offers an organisation the opportunity to utilise my skills for assistance with special projects or perform work so staff can undertake other projects or gain extra help at a busy time.

I became interested in this job after searching for job opportunities via recruitment website, it really appealed to me as a Commercial student with a strong commitment to sustainable management practices in Finance or Logistic and I have a desire to support the company.

I am used to work as Business Assistant at the foreign company, I arranged and managed job easier. At the same time, interpersonal and time management skills were also developed effectively. And the position of Inbound / Outbound at Tiki Join Stock company is more related to the field of this job. Both of it brought me the growth in management, course/plan designing or public speaking skills. Furthermore, I am a Leader of two big contest with different scale: multi-university and nation contest. I regularly worked with a high pressuere of numbers, thus, it helps me develop meticulousness skills and "diagnose" the problems in business of company needs to improve comvenience and reduce overhead cost's company.

You will find me to be a positive, motivated person who is keen to learn and contribute to company. Given the opportunity, I would apply myself with enthusiasm to all tasks, ensuring that I get the job done accurately and efficiently.

As part of my application, I have attached my resume for your consideration. I will follow up this letter with an email to see if you would like any further information. Thank you for considering my request.

Your Applicant

Tran Phuoc Tho